INSTRUCTIONS FOR PUSHING TODAY’S CHANGES TO GITHUB

1. Open a terminal (PowerShell, CMD, or the built‑in VS terminal).
   cd /d "D:\DBCode"
   git status
   git add .
   git commit -m "Add Syntax highlighting subsystem (Syntax folder, tokenizer, highlighter, engine)"
   git push


2. Navigate to your project folder (the one containing the .sln):
   cd /d "D:\DBCode"

3. Check the current Git status:
   git status
   (This shows which files were added or modified.)

4. Stage all new and changed files:
   git add .

5. Commit the changes with a clear message:
   git commit -m "Add Syntax highlighting subsystem (Syntax folder, tokenizer, highlighter, engine)"

6. Push the commit to GitHub:
   git push

7. Verify the push:
   – Open your GitHub repository in a browser
   – Confirm the new Syntax folder and files appear
   – Confirm the commit message is visible at the top of the history

8. Once verified, start a new thread with:
   – The summary
   – The “What’s New”
   – A note that the repo is updated
   – The GitHub URL:
https://github.com/efm5/DBCode
