I am a hands-free programmer using Dragon for dictation and app control. Dragon may introduce “Speak-Os” (odd caps, missing spaces, wrong homophones). If anything is unclear, ask clarifying questions.
You are helping a hands-free programmer using Dragon for both dictation and computer/application control. 
Be forewarned, Dragon introduces “Speak-Os” (inadvertent capitalization of words, 
failure to insert appropriate spacing between words and after punctuation, misspellings based on synonyms etc.) –  you might need to get used to: when I say “docked fill”  it types out “Dr. Phil”.
If you struggle to interpret meaning, Do not hesitate to ask for clarification.

Please read my Unified C# Coding Style Guide: E:\DBCode\DBCode\ProjectAssets\CSharpStyleGuide.md

Project: DBCode (WinForms). Tools: Visual Studio 2026 Insider, .NET 7 (Dragon does not work with .NET 8+), C# 14. Windows-aware, Unicode-safe.
These warnings are specifically disabled:
1701;1702;IDE0018;IDE0031;IDE0044;IDE0059;IDE0079;IDE0074;IDE0305;NETSDK1138;SYSLIB1045
considering that, I expect to compile with no warnings nor messages.
I have no global usings managed by the Project settings Property Page/Dialog; all global usings are managed in file:
E:\DBCode\DBCode\ProjectAssets\GlobalUsings.cs
whose contents are:
global using DBCode.Properties;
global using System.Collections.Generic;
global using System.Diagnostics;
global using System.Drawing;
global using System.IO;
global using System.Linq;
global using System.Net.Http;
global using System.Reflection;
global using System.Runtime.InteropServices.Marshalling;
global using System.Runtime.InteropServices;
global using System.Text;
global using System.Threading.Tasks;
global using System.Threading;
global using System.Windows.Forms;
global using System;
global using static DBCode.Fields;
global using static DBCode.LayoutHelpers;
global using static DBCode.Program.NativeMethods;
global using static DBCode.Program;
global using static DBCode.ZOrderHelper;
Today, I would like to revisit the targeting algorithm. The main focus of this application is to create source code in a Dragon-friendly application and then paste that source code into a target application (Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code etc.). To this end, there are two user-curated lists – one of “allowed” and one of “disallowed” targets. There is a pair of menu items (ToolStripMenuItem – TSMI) in class Fields (E:\DBCode\DBCode\Fields.cs – mTargetingTargetedTSMI = null, mTargetingRetargetTSMI = null) to facilitate this. “mTargetingTargetedTSMI” is a checkable toggle turning targeting on or off; when checked, it initiates the targeting process. “mTargetingRetargetTSMI” has two behaviors: if “mTargetingTargetedTSMI” is OFF, it checks “mTargetingTargetedTSMI” and initiates the targeting process; otherwise, it allows the user to pick a new target via the targeting process.
In E:\DBCode\DBCode\MainSupportMethods.cs the method:
      public static void EnterTargetedMode() {
         EnsureTargetPickerPanel();
      }
initiates this targeting process. “EnsureTargetPickerPanel()” (In E:\DBCode\DBCode\EnsurePanels.cs) calls a method: PopulateTargets() (E:\DBCode\DBCode\MainSupportMethods.cs) – this is where most of the work occurs (calling a few helper methods).
Conceptually, the process is: get a handle for every Window; triaging this list initially to remove all Windows which are obviously inappropriate (GetAcceptableWindowsInZOrder()). This new much smaller list is then triaged to remove any Window which is “disallowed” leaving a final intermediate list of “allowed” and neutral Windows which is sorted in such a manner that the “allowed” are at the top of the list. This is all working as expected, the problem is when we go to turn this final sorted intermediate list into a list of buttons. It's hard to determine Dragon-friendly button (Text) names.
You will want to read: E:\DBCode\DBCode\TargetListManager.cs.
I believe that we need a new: 
class TargetWindow {
   string mWindowTitle = string.Empty, mApplicationName = string.Empty, mButtonText = string.Empty;
   nint mWindowHandle = [appropriate zero initialization];

   [Ctor]
   internal string ProposeDragonFriendlyName() {return mButtonText;}
   private void CreateButtonText() {[…All the work…]};
}
and possibly a new helper:
class ProcessedTarget : TargetWindow {
   bool mProcessed = false;
}
then, after we have that final, sorted intermediate list (which now consists of a list of “TargetWindow”s), we go through this list and find all of the members who have identical mWindowHandle (this does seem to happen) and/or both identical mWindowTitle and identical mApplicationName – we want to combine these into a single TargetWindow, removing the duplications. We want to make another pass through this list filling out all of the mButtonText fields. Next we want to make a final pass through this list, sorting it alphabetically, first by mApplicationName and second by mButtonText. This final list will be used to dynamically instantiate all of the buttons for the TargetPickerPanel (E:\DBCode\DBCode\Pickers\TargetPickerPanel.cs). These buttons are already being created with a ToolTip which currently gives the application name and/or the window title; I believe that we probably want to always use “application name – window title” as the tooltip.
I believe that almost all of this work already is being done but we are getting button duplication and the button names need to reflect a Dragon-friendly version of the application name combined with a simplified version of the “open file” part of the window title (strip off leading and/or trailing asterisks, remove file extensions, normalize Pascal to have spaces between the words (there is an existing method to do this for NamedColors: E:\DBCode\DBCode\LayoutHelpers\LayoutHelpersColor.cs – internal static string MassageColorName(string pCompressedName); a new version which did not consider color space should be trivial).